♪Subtitles by♪  XQ2☻♥
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
File 82-712:
Agent Rick Dicker interrogating.
State your name, please.
Uh... Tony.
Tony Rydinger.
Tell me about the incident.
Well, there's this girl in my class.
I saw her at the track meet.
- You're Violet, right?
- That's me.
I sorta knew her, but she'd changed.
For better.
She was more sure of herself, cool, cute.
I asked her out for a movie.
- So, Friday?
- Friday.☻
And then I went to watch the track meet.
Not long after, this 'thing'
happened in the parking lot.
Behold, the Underminer!
I am always beneath you,
but nothing is beneath me.
As if things aren't weird enough,
I look over and I see these boots.
- You two stay here.
- Wait, should we be doing this?
It is still illegal.
It looked like super heroes.
- We're going to lose him.
- Oh, all right.
One of you control the perimeter,
keep the crowd back and safe.
The other watch after Jack-jack.
- But, I thought we were gonna...
- You heard your mother.
Trampoline me.
I call perimeter.
You're not going anywhere.
Come back here!
I see my chance to get out of there.
But, there's something familiar
about one of the kids' voices.
The girl, she's upset, and
she throws down her mask,
and it's her!
Oh, Tony!
Hi. This isn't what you think it is.
This was getting too freaky
I couldn't handle it and ran off.
I feel kinda bad about it.
Maybe I should've said, hi, or something.
It's not her fault superheroes are illegal.
And it's not like I don't like
strong girls,
I'm pretty secure, manhood-wise...
What is that?
Have you told anyone else about this?
Your parents?
No, they'd only think
I was high on something.
- I think you know what I mean.
- Sure, kid.
I like this girl, Mr. Dicker,
I'm supposed to go out
with her Friday night.
Now things are just gonna be weird.
I wish I could forget I ever saw her
in that suit.
You will, kid.
You will.
[INCREDIBLES 2]
Come on!
Consider yourselves undermined!
- Underminer, we meet again!
- Huh?
Oh, great! Now he's on the agenda.
Oh!
Incredible,...
meet Jackhammer!
(...)*
Bye-bye!
No no no...
Everyboy, stand back, okay?
Stay back!
Dash, can't you see we're babysitting.
I can't steer it, or stop it
and the Underminer's escaped.
We'll have to stop it...
Bob, the monorail!
Frozone! Yeah!
We have to stop this thing
before it gets to the overpass.
I'll try to keep it away
from the buildings.
Hey, lady!
Thank you so much, young man.
Violet!
Stop!
Everybody stop!
- Heads up, dad!
- Dash!
- Violet, who's watching Jack-Jack?
- Dad's watching him.
Violet, here, you take him.
It's headed for City Hall.
Mom needs help.
They're out in public again.
This is our chance!
Follow them.
Follow Frozone!
Bob!
Help me with the boiler.
That should do it.
What are you kids doing?
Get outta here!
This thing's gonna blow!
There's no time!
We did it!
Freeze, supers!
Oh, what did we do!
Excuse me, Mr. 'Zone?
Sorry, but, I'm not really
supposed to be here.
Which seems wrong, doesn't it?
Perhaps you'd be interested in
changing that law?
Superheroes, including Frozone,
Mr. Incredible and Elastigirl,
caused further damage to the city.
The Underminer remains at large.
- We didn't start this fight.
- Well, you didn't finish it, either!
- Dd you stop Underminer from
inflicting more damage? - No.
- Did you stop him from robbing
the banks? - No.
- Did you catch him?
- No.
The banks were insured, we
have infrastructure in place
to deal with these matters.
If you had simply done nothing,
everything would now be
proceeding in an orderly fashion.
You'd have preferred we do nothing?
Without a doubt.
You weren't much help.
You want out of the hole?
First you gotta put down
the shovel.
Uh, that went poorly.
Dad, this is probably
not the best time
to tell you about this, but,
something else happened today:
about a kid, and my mask.
Oh hey, Rick, Violet's friend,
a kid named Tony,
might have seen her in the outfit
without her mask.
- Talkative type?
- Dunno, last name is Rydinger.
Tony Rydinger. I'll check it out.
Bob, Helen.
A word if you don't mind.
The program's been shut down.
What?
Politicians don't understand
people who do good
simply because it's right.
Makes them nervous.
They've been gunning
for supers for years.
Today was all they needed.
Anyway, I'm done.
I'm afraid two more weeks in the motel
was the best I can do for you.
- It's ain't much.
- You've done plenty, Rick.
We won't forget it.
Well, it has been a great honor
working with you good people.
Thanks for everything. And good luck.
Yeah, you too.
Did you wash your hands?
With the soap?
Did you dry them?
What?! Is this all vegetables?
Who ordered all vegetables?
I did. They're good and
you're going to have some.
Are we going to talk about it?
- What?
- The elephant in the room.
- What elephant?
- I guess not, then.
- You're referring to today?
- Yeah! What's the deal with today?
We all make mistakes.
For example, you kids were
supposed to watch Jack-Jack.
Babysitting, while you guys
did the important stuff.
We talked about this.
You're not old enough to decide
about these things.
- We are old enough to help out.
- Yeah!
Isn't that what you tell us, dad?
Yeah, well, help out can mean
many different things.
- But we're supposed to help
if there's trouble. - Yeah.
- Aren't you glad we helped today?
- I know, but...
- You said that you were proud of us.
- Well, I was, 'am'.
We wanna fight bad guys!
No, you don't!
You said things were different, now.
And they were 'on the island'.
But, I didn't mean that from now on...
So, now, we gotta go back to
never using our powers!
- It defines who I am!
- We're not saying...
- What?
- Someone on TV said it.
Can we just eat the dinner,
while it's hot?
Did we do something wrong?
- Yes. - No.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Superheroes are illegal.
Whether it's fair or not,
that's the law.
The law should be fair.
What are we teaching our kids?
- To respect the law.
- Even when the law is disrepectful?
If laws are unjust, there are laws to
change them. Otherwise it's chaos.
Which is exactly what we have!
- I just thought it was kinda cool.
- What was?
Fighting crime as a family.
It was cool.
But, it's over.
The world is what it is.
We have to adapt.
Are things bad?
Things are fine.
Can I be excused?
How much longer in the motel, dad?
Not much longer, sweetie.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
- Maybe Dicker will find something.
- Dicker is gone, Bob.
Any thought we had about
being supers again, is fantasy.
One of us has gotta get a job.
One of us?
You did a long stint at Insuricare.
- Hated every minute of it.
- I know it was hard on you.
Maybe it's my turn in the
private sector and you take...
No, I'm doing this.
I need to do this.
- Do you know where suit and my ties are?
- Burned up when...
- the jet destroyed our house.
Yeah.
We can't count on anyone
else now, Bob. It's just us.
We can't wait for...
No lifeguard on duty.
Swim at your own risk.
Oh, where'd you go today?
I noticed you missed all the fun.
Don't be mad, because I know
when to leave a party.
I'm just as illegal as you guys, besides
I knew the cops would let you go.
- Yeah. In spite of Bob's best efforts.
- Yeah, yeah.
I heard the program shut down.
- How much longer are you in this motel?
- 2 weeks.
And you know the offer still stands.
You're very generous,
but there's five of us.
We wouldn't do that
to you and Honey.
The door's always open.
You know the news isn't all bad.
While you guys were
being detained,
I was approached by a dude
who represents this tycoon.
Winston Deavor.
Wants to talk with me,
with you too, about hero stuff.
I checked him out, he's legit,
trained under Dicker,
he wants to meet.
Aw, jeez, more Superhero trouble?
We just came from the police
station Lucius.
- When?
- Tonight, I'm going there, now.
You enjoy. I'm sittin' this one out.
He wants all three of us.
Honey, let's just, at least
hear what he has to say.
You got the address,
I'll meet you guys there.
We go in our supersuits?
Yeah. Might wanna wear the old supersuits.
Got a feeling he's nostalgic.
Where are you going?
The fresh air is
especially good tonight.
- If Jack-Jack wakes up...
- I know the drill.
Your security badge.
Please this way.
Hey listen, you're my biggest fan.
What am I saying? I'm your biggest...
Shoot.
I love superheroes!
The powers, the costumes,
the mythic struggles!
Winston Deavor. You can call me Win.
Genuine pleasure to meet you.
Frozone!
- Elastigirl.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mr. Incredible.
- Hello.
♪ Mr. Incredible,
Incredible, Incredible.
♪ Catching the bad guys,
♪ pow, pow, pow!
♪ Who's the cat that got the skill
♪ When survival odds are close to nil?
♪ Frozone, Frozone.
♪ Frozone!
Yeah!
Can't tell you what
a thrill this is.
- And this is ...
- Oh, hello there.
Superheroes, I'm so sorry.
...is my TARDY sister, Evelyn.
And I'm scolding myself, so,
you don't have to, Winston.
Spectacular.
My father was so proud
that I was even remotely
connected to you guys.
He used to call you,
the last line of defense.
He was your top supporter.
He donated to superhero causes,
he raised money for the
Dynaguy statue in Avery Park.
He got to know many supers, personally.
Even installed a phone
with direct lines
to Gazerbeam and Bionic
in case of emergencies.
He loved that.
Showed it off to everyone.
He was heartbroken when you were
all forced to go underground.
Father believed the world be
more dangerous without you.
But, you know how right he was.
There was a break-in.
My father called Gazerbeam,
the direct line.
No answer.
He called Bionic.
Superheroes had just been made illegal.
The robbers discovered him
on the phone, and shot him.
So...
Must've been hard.
Especially for mother.
She died a few months later.
Heartbreak.
If superheroes had not been forced
underground it never would've happened.
Or dad could've taken mom to his safe-room
as soon as he knew there was trouble.
I disagree strongly, but we're
not going into it right now.
The point is nobody expected us
to be able to actually
run dad's company.
But with Evelyn as designer,
and myself as operator,
we threw ourselves into building
Devtech into what it is today.
A world-class
telecommunications company.
Bigger than ever.
and perfectly positioned to
make some wrong things, right.
Hence, this meeting.
Let me ask you something.
What is the main you were
all forced underground?
- Ignorance.
- Perception.
Take today, for example,
with the Underminer.
Difficult situation: you were faced
with a lot of hard decisions.
- Oh, tell me about it.
- I can't.
Because, I didn't see it.
Neither did anyone else.
So, when you fight bad guys, like today,
people don't see the fight,
or what led up to it.
They see what politicians
tell them to see.
They see the destruction,
and they see you.
So if we want change people's
perceptions about superheroes,
we need YOU to share YOUR
perceptions with the world.
- How do we do that?
- With cameras.
we need YOU to share YOUR
perceptions with the world.
How do we do that?
We embed tiny cameras like those
into your super suit.
Wow, so small!
- And the picture is outstanding.
- Thanks, I designed it myself.
We've got resources, lobbyists, world-wide
connections and, very important,
- Insurance.
- Insurance is key.
All we need now,
are the superest superheroes.
It means you three.
Come on, help me make
all supers legal again!
This sounds great!
Let's get this going,
what's my first assignment?
That enthusiasm is golden.
Hold onto it.
But for our first move, well,
Elastigirl is our best play.
- Better than me?
- Ahem!
I mean, she's good.
She's, really, a credit to her, but...
you know ... You know.
With great respect,
let's not test the whole,
'insurance-will-pay-for-everything' idea,
on the first go 'round, OK?
Wait a minute, you're saying what?
I'm messy?
Well, Evelyn did a cost-benefit
analysis comparing
all your last 5 years of crime-fighting,
before going underground.
And Elastigirl's numbers
are self-explanatory.
Oh, it's not a fair comparison.
Heavyweight problems,
need heavyweight solutions.
Of course! We're gonna solve
all kinds of problems together.
After a perfect launch with Elastigirl!
- So, what do you say?
- What do I say?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
A few hours ago, you were saying
it was over.
That being a superhero
was a fantasy.
Now, you get the offer of a lifetime
and you don't know?
It's not that simple, Bob.
I wanna protect the kids.
- So do I.
- From jail, Bob!
How do you do that?
By turning down the chance
to change the law that's forcing
them to hide what they are?
They haven't decided what they are!
They're still kids.
Kids with powers,
which makes them supers.
Whether they decide to use
those powers, or not.
- This will benefit them.
- Look, it's not a good time to be away.
Dashiel's having trouble
with homework,
Violet's worried about her first
date with that boy she likes, Tony.
- And Jack-Jack ...
- Jack-Jack? What's wrong with him?
OK, nothing's wrong with Jack-Jack.
But, even a normal baby
needs a lot of attention.
- I'm just not sure I can leave.
- Of course you can leave.
You've got to, so that I...
WE could be supers, again.
So, our kids can have that choice.
- So you can have that choice.
- All right, yes!
So I can have that choice.
And I would do a great job.
Regardless of what those dumb
pie charts say, or whatever.
But they want you.
And you'll do a great...
job.
Sure.
That was excruciating to watch.
I can't lie to you,
it's nice to be wanted.
- Flattery, you know. But...
- What's the choice?
1: do this right, get well paid,
we're out of the motel,
and things get better for all supers,
including our kids.
Or, 2: I find a job in two weeks
or we're homeless.
You know it's crazy, right?
To help my family, I gotta leave it.
To fix the law, I gotta break it.
- You'll be great.
- I know I will.
- But what about you? We have kids.
- I'll watch the kids. No problem.
- Easy.
- Easy, huh? You're adorable.
Well, if there is a problem, I'll drop
this thing and come right back.
You won't need to.
I got it, you go. Do this thing.
Do it so,...
I can do it better.
- Deavor, here.
- This is Elastigirl, I'm in.
Mr. Deavor, it's wonderful,
but, it's too generous.
Nonsense. It's the least we could do.
We're partners, now!
Can't have my partners living in a motel.
Wh-whose is the house?
It's my house. I have several.
I'm not using that one.
Stay as long as you need.
- I don't know what to say.
- How about, thanks?
This is our new house?!
It's OK, easy, tiger.
It's being loaned to us.
- Yeah. - This is homey.
- I mean, look at this place.
Deavor bought it from an
eccentric billionaire
who liked to come and go,
without being seen,
so the house has
multiple hidden exits.
Good thing we won't stand out.
Wouldn't wanna attract any
unecessary attention.
It's got a big yard!
- Isn't... Isn't it a bit much?
- Near a forest!
- Would you rather be at the motel?
- And a pool!
What exactly is mom's new job?
The important thing is,
we're out of the motel.
I like mom's new job!
Oho, hohoh!
Woah!
Wow, check out the water features!
This is cool!
Hey!
Stop!
Stop it!
Watch out!
No!
This isn't me!
And w-what is this...
I'm not all dark and angst-y,
I'm Elastigirl!
I'm, you know, flexible.
I mean...
- E designed this?
- No.
Some guy named Alexander Galbaki.
Glad it's you and not me,
'cause you're gonna hear from her*.
- This note came with it.
- What?
[Elastigirl, an accessory
is in the garage. Evelyn]
A new new Elasticycle.
Elasticycle? I didn't
know you had a bike.
Hey, I had a Mohawk. There's a
lot about me, you don't know.
You had a Mohawk?
Eh, you didn't miss anything.
Oh, yeah! This one's electric.
What's that mean?
Means that... oops!
Ah, I'll get the hang of it.
- You will be great.
- I will be great.
- And you will, too.
- We will both be great.
Bye sweetie.
- Wait a minute, is that Elastigirl?
- That's Elastigirl.
Hey, Elastigirl!
Here comes, Elastigirl.
That's fine. Stay calm, or
I'll turn this bus right 'round.
Look at that, New Urban!
You wanna make a big
crime-fighting statement?
You go where the crime
is biggest.
Strange thing, to be excited
about, Winston.
It's, like, a superheroes' playground.
No sugar-bombs on my watch.
- Where's momr?
- She's up and out.
She's at her new job,
doing hero work.
- But, I thought superheroes
were still illegal.
They are, for now.
So, mom is getting paid
to break the law?
She's not break...
She's an advocate for superheroes.
It's a new job.
So, mom is going out, illegally,
to explain, why she shouldn't
be illegal.
Hey... HEY! The bus is here!
Woah! Grab your stuff! Go on, get on the...
Put your homework in your bag.
Bye-bye.
We're gonna get along, just fine.
'Cause you don't ask any
hard questions
All right, all locations.
- We need to know where you want us.
- OK, I'm right at...
Feels strange, though,
waiting for a crime.
Relax, you're smack in the middle of
the worst crime area in ​​the city.
It's perfect.
- It's a superheroes' playground.
- Superheroes' playground, right.
You know, after we went
underground,
my husband used to listen
to a police scanner.
Waiting for something to happen.
And I got mad at him for it.
Ooh, I'm such a hypocrite.
- All units ...
- Something's up.
I'm picking up some chatter
about potential disruptions
to the Hover-train's
opening ceremony.
Disruption or threat?
Both. Station's at 54th
and Nottingham.
A potential threat. Perfect!
54th and Nottingham. Go, go, go!
Vi, I want you back here by 10:30.
- 11-ish?
- 10-ish.
-  Heading for 9:30-ish.
- 10:30-ish it is.
Hm. Enjoy the movie.
In the county of Nanar,
the frubbers of Freep
are all giving in,
to the sweet succour of sleep.
We will control the horizontal.
We will control the vertical.
[NEW MATH]
We can roll the image.
That's not the way you're
supposed to do it, dad.
They want us to do it this...
I don't know that way.
Why would they change math?
- It's okay, dad.
- Math is math. Math is math!
I'll just wait for mom to get back.
What? Well, she won't understand
it any better than I do!
The Outer Limits.
All over Duzzeldorf,
the Fribbers of Frupp
are going to sleep 'cause
they just can't keep up.
All over Duzzeldorf,
Duzzels are drowsy.
Their eyelids so heavy...
OK! The point is, everyone,
everyone's hitting the sack.
Everyone's getting the sleep
that they lack.
Mayors often brag about their
city, and I'm no exception.
And I'm going to admit that...
Are you sure the police are
gonna be okay with this?
Sure, you're making life easy for'em.
They still haven't forgiven us for the
last time we made life easy for them.
I know the chief of police,
that won't be a problem.
With all due respect, if you alone
had handled the Underminer,
things would have
been different.
I'm just sayin'.
And now... to launch our
magnificent, new hover-train.
It can get you where
you need to go,
at ridiculous speeds.
The future is open for business!
Wait, the train just stopped.
- Woah!
- What?
It's going the wrong direction.
We're going the wrong way.
I'm going after it.
This thing's really moving!
100 and climbing.
How much track is built?
About 25 miles.
Nobody can shut this thing down?
They've tried, no go.
Is that Elastigirl?
Look out!
- Override!
- They're locked out of the system.
- What about a fail-safe.
- Not enough time.
- Someone's calling?
- Switch it over.
Hey, mom, I can't find my high socks,
and dad can't find them either
but he won't call you and ask, so, I am.
You're not calling your mother!
Dash, honey, can't talk right now.
But look under your bed, OK?
- How much time?
- Approximately 2 minutes.
There's a shortcut
through the corridor up ahead.
I dunno if I can stay with him.
Come on!
What the heck?
Everybody alright? Is anybody injured?
You alright?
Your story better be good!
Hey? HEY?
What happened?
[Welcome back, Elastigirl]
.
[Screenslaver]
- Honey, why are you?...
- Don't say anything.
- It's dad. Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Tony didn't even call?
- Oh honey... - Dad!
If you want me to feel better,
then, leave me alone. Please.
Huh?
...only my kid brother's son.
Today is his first birthday.
He's not as mature, as you, Roy.
'Cause you're a wonderful policeman.
This is a holdup.
Right, get your hands up,
turn your back.
Put your hands behind your head
and keep'em there. Don't move.
Drop it! And get over there.
Watch the door.
Do you think I'm kiddin'?
Now.
- I said, now!
- I got'im!
Come on!
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
No, no!
No, no, no! NO!
No, no, no, no! NO!
You have POWERS!
Yeah, baby!
And there's not a scratch
on you!
How'd you go through the locked door?
Are those your powers?
You can multiply like rabbits and
go right through anything solid.
Oh, my God!
- Hello.
- Hey, honey. You weren't gonna call me?
Hi, hey, no. I mean, yes, yeah.
I just didn't wanna... wait.
The strangest thing just
happened out in the yard.
Sounds like I just woke you up.
No, no, it's just, Jack-Jack.
He's had an accident? I knew it.
I'm coming home, right now.
- I never should've...
- No, no, no. No accidents.
Stay there and
finish your mission.
And you never, should... What?!
You don't think I can do this?
Sorry, I misspoke.
Do you need me to come back?
No, no, no, I've got this.
Everything's great.
What happened with Jack-Jack?
- Nothing, he's in excellent health.
- Well, that's good.
How was Violet's date?
That was tonight, right?
Oh, yeah. Yes. Good.
All, fine, and good.
And Jack-Jack went down,
with no trouble?
Fine, yes, no trouble.
And Dash got his homework done?
- All done. - So, things haven't spiraled
out of control, the moment I left?
Amazing as it may seem, it has
been quite uneventful, in fact.
How about you?
I saved a runaway train!
It was so great! The mayor was there
to cut the ribbon on this new train.
...opening ceremony,
Elastigirl pursued the train
and was able to
successfully activate...
Bla-bla-bla, he says a few
words, cut the ribbon
and the train starts pulling
out of the station, backwards, then...
- the track of the brand new hover-train
- ...the train malfunctioned
- ...due to Elastigirl...
- ...came to an almost...
...superhero. Elastigirl...
- Elastigirl... - Elastigirl...
BOOM! NO CASUALTIES!
...specialized motorbike...
And I go after it, I'm tellin'ya
honey, it was a saga!
That's fantastic honey!
And on your first night!
I'm so proud of you. Really.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I know you wanna get out there
and you will soon, OK?
You will be amazing!
I couldn't have done this,
if you hadn't taken over so well.
Thanks for handling everything.
It's nothing.
I love you, honey. I'll be back soon.
- Sweet dreams.
- Sweet dreams, honey.
...I can't explain...
Hey, dad, it's okay.
I'll just wait for mom to get home.
As if she could... ah...
I can do math.
Oh, that's not a good sign...
Weak command!
Am I a substitute parent?
It's not my fault, they changed math.
Hey, buddy. Come on.
I think I understad your
math assignment.
We still have some time to
finish it before your test.
First, you wanna put all the
numbers by themselves....
And now that means the
plus becomes a minus and the minus....
You got it? Yeah, baby!
Oh. Hello.
We're in a new house.
I did write my address
on your locker,
in permanent ink.
Oh, is that, what that is?
Did you forget?
Forget? ... What?
That's funny.
Funny for honey.
Oh, was it the weird outfit?
'Cause there's a reason!
I'm in a drama class,
and they just wanna
do Shakespeare,
but they were like, try to
make it relevant for the kids.
So, like, superheroes.
Kids love superheroes. - Yeah, yeah.
You wanna wear one
kind of tights
and then they're like, no,
wear these other kind.
Do... Do I know you?
Many say your speech today
is critical.
Both sides just want the
best for their people.
We are so close to finally
getting peace in the region.
I haven't done this in a while.
This is good.
The train gives us momentum.
Just go out there and be your
charming self and capitalize.
Ms. Elastigirl, they're ready for you.
Hey, spread your legs.
- Thank you Chad.
- My pleasure, Ambassador.
Gloria.
Madam Ambassador, hello!
You are Elastigirl! This is why,
now, I'm shaking your hands.
Oh, I was so sad when
you went ungerground.
I'm glad to see you back!
In your shiny outfit.
- That means so much coming from you.
Good luck with your speech.
- Bring lasting peace.
- I will, when you defeat evil!
Okay.
Three, two ...
For over 15 years, superheroes
have been in hiding.
Forced into it by a society,
no longer willing to support them.
That may soon be changing due to a
growing movement to bring supers back.
Here, fresh on the heels of her own
heroic save of a runaway train
and sporting a new look,
is the superhero, Elastigirl.
- Welcome. - Hello, Chad. - Well all the
polls are going in your direction.
That's true. Things are good.
Hello.
Uh, hello.
Do I have your attention?
Yes, Chad?
Of course, I do,
I'm appearing on your screen.
Reading the words I'm saying
off of another screen.
Screens are everywhere.
We are controlled by screens.
And screens are controlled by me:
SCREENSLAVER!
- Hey!
- I control this broadcast.
And this idiotic anchorman
you see before you.
- What's wrong with him?
- The signal's been hijacked!
- I'll check it out.
- Don't look at any monitors.
I could hijack the ambassador's
aerocade,
while it's still airborne,
right, Elastigirl?
Nearest window!
Where's the nearest window?
There.
- What's going on?
- Where's Elastigirl?
Which one?
- What are you doing here?
- The Ambassador is in danger.
Which chopper is she in?
Look out!
Follow them and get me close!
Get out of the sky. Touchdown safely!
Stand down, it's Elastigirl.
Stay in your seat, Ma'am!
We're under attack!
Quick go.
Protect the Ambassador!
- Open the door!
- Do as she says!
- Can you all, swim?
- Yeah. - Yeah. - No.
We're gonna have to switch sides, hang on!
Are you all right, Ma'am?
I'm perfectly fine.
Boys are dirt and superheroes suck.
- Good morning.
- He took one look at me in that suit,
and decided to pretend
he doesn't even know me.
Oh, he's protecting himself.
If he really see you,
it's best that he forgets.
It's better for you, too.
I can't tell you how many
memories
Dicker's had to erase,
over the years, when...
someone figured out your
mother's or my identity.
It was Dicker!
- You told him about Tony!
- Honey.
You had me erased from
Tony's mind!
I hate superheroes!
And I renounce them!
I renounce th...!
Is she having adolescence?
a new report out
today shows that
when it comes to decision making
people have more trust in a monkey
throwing darts than Congress.
What's going on Tommy? The President?
They're here in support.
Support? Support for what?
In support of you.
Hello, all of you!
Thanks for coming out. Hi.
Oh, my goodnes, thanks so much!
Hello. What's your sign say?
[SCREENSLAVER IS STILL OUT THERE]
'Sup?
Oh, what do you know, Ellen Wood!
Oh, now you wanna return my calls
about superheroes, huh?
Oh, I'll have to call YOU back.
Oh, that felt good!
Felicia, hold my calls, please.
Hey, it's working!
Hey, the ambassador made a big
speech about superheroes, today.
Turns out, saving someone's life makes
a good impression on them. Who knew?
I'm getting calls from
all over the world.
Media awareness is up 72%
The push for superhero
legalization's becoming
a world-wide movement!
I have big plans for our next move.
We're gonna have a summit at sea.
We'll use our ship we'll gather
leaders
and supers from all over
the world.
That's great. I'm happy.
I'm happy the numbers are up.
I'm happy the ambassador is
pro-superheroes.
And I'm happy, you're happy.
I'm hearing that you're happy,
but why am I not feeling it?
Because I didn't get him.
Screenslaver's still out there.
All I did was play his game
and win this round.
He's gonna want more and as long
as he gets to play, he wins!
One thing I've learned in business:
smell the flowers.
They don't bloom that often.
What do you want on your tombstone,
"She worried a lot"?
All right, stop talking,
show her.
Wow, ah...
Wow! Elastigirl, there you are.
- Hello.
- I-I didn't... wow!
Ahem! (Get yourself together, Karen)
Hi, my superhero name is Voyd,
I just wanna thank you, for like,
for being you.
And I'd... really like to say... Okay.
What I can do, um, is this.
Yeah, that is impressive
Very interdimensional.
I felt like an outcast. Before.
But now, with you being... you.
I really...
Yay, me.
I flew them in, from all over.
They've all been in hiding.
With powers, secret identities,
and
names they've given themselves.
I'm Screech, a pleasure.
I always considered you as
the gold standard for the superhero.
Well, thanks. You're too nice.
- I am called Brick.
- Nice to meet you, Brick.
- Where are you from?
- Winsconsin.
Oh, Elastigirl. I assume your powers are...
You know, zapping things electrically,
charging things, bolts of lightning,
that kinda stuff.
Name's Reflux.
Medical condition, or superpower?
You decide.
That's a little line I say
just to put people at ease.
- By the way: big fan.
- Oh, no, no.
Reflux, love it.
Yeah, that is impressive.
Keep practicing.
Ow!
Well, I'm beat.
Congratulations. Big day.
Good night ladies.
I will see you tomorrow.
G'night.
Must be nice for you,
being out front,
- after all this time?
- Out front?
Well, it's been a while
since your superhero days.
And, even then, you were kind of
in Mr. Incredible's shadow.
Nah, I beg to differ.
I'm not saying you weren't big.
And you were and ARE a superstar.
But, you have the stage
to yourself, now.
People have to pay attention, now.
You mean it's a man's
world and all that bull?
What world do you live in?
- Your brother runs Devtech.
- I don't want his job.
I invent. He sells.
I ask you, which of us has
the greater influence?
Which side of me are you asking?
The believer or the cynic?
- The cynic.
- Would say, selling is more important
because the best sellers
have the most buyers.
Doesn't matter what you're selling.
It only matters what people buy.
This is true. If I discovered
the origin of the universe,
my brother would find a way
to market it as a...
foot massager.
So, what would the believer say?
The believer would tell you
to make your mark.
Don't wait for permission,
assert yourself
and impose your will
on the status quo.
- Sounds like my brother.
- What?
- You sound like my brother.
- Well, he's not wrong.
There's an art to
getting a reaction.
- Oh, I know how to get him!
- My brother?
Which... No! Screenslaver!
You're tech savvy; I need to lock
onto his signal and trace its origin.
How fast can you slap something
together and meet me at the airport?
- Airport?
- Need to get out of town, pronto.
I can get your contraption
together by 5:am.
We need to get on TV. Chad!
I'll get my brother to set up an exclusive
with him tonight on the newscast
- Finish our interview by phone!
- Promote the hell out of it!
Independent from screen slavery!
'Chad Tonight. BOOM!'
- Dicker.
- Yeah, hey Rick.
You remember that kid I mentioned
to you, Tony Rydinger?
Mind-wipe? Yeah, nice kid.
Well, you also wiped out a Friday
night date, my daughter had with him.
In fact, you wiped out my daughter.
Oops. Not an exact science, Bob
Rick, you gotta help me here.
Violet hates me, and you,
and superheroes.
I gotta fix this.
What do you know about Tony?
Er... Not much. Seems like a good kid.
Popular, plays sports, music.
Parents own the 'Happy Platter'.
Kid works there, part-time.
Happy Platter?
Why did we drive all the way across
town for the 'Happy Platter'?
We'd like a booth, over there,
near the Philodendron.
Good, right, near the Philodendron?
This platter doesn't look
all that happy, to me.
It looks bored.
The Bored Platter!
I thought Vi would want a change
of pace from drive-in food.
I like drive-in food.
Does this mean, vegetables?
A balanced diet needs vegetables,
kiddo. Get ussed to it.
Good evening, everyone.
- OH!
- Gross!
- Is she all right?
- Yeah, it's OK.
- Let me help you. - That's fine sir.
- I'm fine! I'm fine!
Normally she doesn't ever drink like that.
OK, would you like
some water, sir?
Yes. Yes, I would.
This is my daughter, whom,
you must know, right?
- Hello. - (Violet).
- Hello, Violet.
- Hey, Vi, say hi to...
- Don't push it, dad!
I'm Dash, her little brother.
Hello.
Really good water, very refreshing!
- Spring water, is it?
- I don't know, sir, I think it's tap.
- Well, it is very good.
- Excellent tap.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
Where'd she go?
To find a good place to be angry?
Tonight, we go now to a special
remote interview with Elastigirl.
How you feeling, Chad? You doing all right?
I'm fine.
The doctors checked me out.
I have no memory of the event.
I gotta tell you, it's pretty strange
to see a recording of yourself
the night before, and
have no recollection
I don't think anyyone needs to worry,
we've taken many precautions tonight.
- Where are you, right now?
- On a case.
In a secure undisclosed location.
I want to talk about you,
starting with your save
of a runaway train.
Here's an exclusive, unedited
clip, from your own suit-cam.
Roll the clip.
This thing's really moving.
100 and climbing.
How much track is built?
Around 25 miles.
Screenslaver interrupts this program
for an important announcement.
I'll be damned, she knew!
Let's see if her gadget works.
- Don't bother wathing the rest...
- Gotcha!
Elastigirl doesn't save the day.
She only postpones her defeat.
And whie she postpones
her defeat,
you eat chips and watch her
confront problems
that you are too lazy to deal with.
Superheroes are part of
your brainless desire
to replace true experiences
with stimulation.
You don't talk,
you watch talk-shows.
You have craving to watch
game shows.
Travel, relationships, risk,
every meaningful experience
must be packaged and
delivered to you to watch at a distance,
so that you can remain ever
sheltered, ever passive,
ever ravenous consumers
who can't bring themseves
to rise from their couches,
break a sweat and participate
in life.
You want superheroes
to protect you,
and make yourselves ever more
powerless in the process,
while you tell yourselves
you're being looked after,
that your futures are being
served and your rights are being upheld.
So that the system can keep
stealing from you,
smiling at you all the while.
Go ahead, send your supers
to stop me.
Grab your snacks, watch your
screens and see what happens.
You are no longer in control,
I am.
Find anything?
Sorry!
What happened?
What happened, is,
you destroyed my evidence!
What's going on? What'd I do?
- What'd you guys do to me?
- That's right punk, blame the system!
Your tracker worked like a charm,
Evelyn, you're a genius.
Aw, shucks! I'm just the genius
behind the genius.
The New Urban city council...
Dad, we're doing fractions and
'dennis-mals' and percentages
- I don't get'em.
- Aren't you ...
- Didn't we get all caught up?
- Yeah, we were caught up
And now, we're doing fractions
and percentages and 'demisals'
Decimals
...of the Incredibile, or the supercar
once driven by superhero,
Mr. Incredible.
It's the kind of thing you buy,
when you have everything else.
They said it was beyond repair.
Hey, it was in perfect condition.
You used to have that?
They said it was destroyed.
Once thought lost or destroyed the
famous car turned up at private auction.
They said it was...
That's my car!
(...stupid car's features...)
This car's just loaded
with amazing gadgets.
- Care to demonstrate?
- I'd love to, but,
we haven't figured out how
to make them work, yet.
Wow! You do that?!
Huh?
What are you doing? This is not a toy!
That's a rocket launcher!
NO WAY?!
Which one launches the rocket?
Hey, this is not your car.
It's not your car, either.
It is, so! It's the Incredibile.
- Well why's that guy have it?
- He shouldn't.
Launch the rocket!
LAUNCH! THE! ROCKET!!
We're not launching anything.
Do you think I want an angry rich
guy coming after me right now,
when I'm trying to not to...
distract...
your mother
Hm... rich guy!...
So you're not gonna steal your car
back from the rich guy?
- Jack-Jack has the powers?
- Well, yeah, but...
- You knew about this?
- Yeah.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- I dunno.
We're your kids.
We need to know these things.
- You tell mom?
- No! - Why not?
Your mother is not
what we're talking about.
- Why not tell mom?
- Because, I didn't want... - What?
- Because, it's not the time.
- Come on, man. - Why?
- Because ...
- It's, so, uncool.
Because I'm formulating OK?
I'm taking in information,
I'm processing.
I'm doing the math,
I'm fixing the boyfriend
and keeping the baby from
turning into a flaming monster.
How do I do it?
By rolling with the punches, baby!
I ain't doing no crash landing, OK?*
'Cause I'm Mr. Incredible,
not Mr. Softsoap, or Mr. Mediocre Guy.
Mr. Incredible!
We should call Lucius.
No! I can handle it.
There's no way I'm gonna...
I'm gonna call Lucius.
Looks normal to me.
When did this start happening?
- Well, since Helen got the job.
- I assume she knows.
Are you kidding?
I can't tell her about this.
Not while she's doing hero work.
Mama.
Girls, come on. Leave the saving
of the world to the men?!
I don't think so!
I've got to succeed so she can succeed.
So we... can succeed.
I get it, Bob. I get it.
When was the last time you slept?
Who keeps track of that?
Besides, he's a baby, I can handle it.
I got this handled.
So... you're good then?
You got everything under control,
right?
What the?!...
Okay, Jack-Jack want a cookie?
Yum-yum, cookie. Jack-Jack...
Yum-yum, cookie.
Cookie.
- You're not?... -  Cookie.
- Oh my God!
Woah, daddy!
So, he can hear you...
from the other dimension. Yeah.
That, is creepy. And that's not good.
Not like our other kids. No, it is not!
Full power: totally random.
So, now he's, what ... is he good?
Yeah, well, you'd think so, right?
Obviously, I can't keep giving him cookies!
But if I stop...
No! No biting, dad. Don't bite!
OK.
I think I just need a little bit of
me time.
Then I'll be good to go.
Oh, you need more than me time, Bob.
You need major life realignment
on a number of levels.
Starting with baby super-freak,
here!
You need some solid
outside the box thinking.
Galbaki?
Elastigirl's supersuit is by Galbaki?!
Explain yourself.
Oh my god, you're worse
than I thought.
It's the baby. I brought the baby.
Highly unusual.
You look ghastly Robert Parr.
I broke my daughter.
They keep changing math.
I need AA batteries, but I got AAAs
So, I still need AA batteries.
Put one red thing with a load of
whites, now everything's pink.
There's not many eggs....
Done properly, parenting is a heroic act.
Done 'properly'.
And fortunately,
it has never affected me.
But, you do not come to me for
eggs and batteries, Robert.
I designing hero wear, and
Elastigirl must have a new suit!
Actually it's Jack-Jack.
You also wish a new suit for the baby?
I would hardly classify this
as an emergency.
Well, it's a special case,
worth studying.
If I could just leave him
with you for a while.
Leave him?! Here?!
I'm not a baby person, Robert.
I have no baby facilties.
I am an artist.
I do not involve myself in
the prosaic day-to-day-to...
day...
Fascinating!
Are you seeing this, Robert?
My God!
Yes.
Of course you can leave the baby
overnight, after all filling in for Helen
is challenging and
you are very tired
and the other children need you and miss
you and need you close to them.
Auntie Edna will take
care of everything
so drive carefully and good bye,
I enjoy our visits.
'Auntie' Edna?
Attention, attention.
I wanna thank everyone
that came out, tonight,
in support of superheroes and
bringing them back into society.
You all made it happen.
And the need for this has
been made crystal clear
in recent days,
with bad actors, like
the self proclaimed Screenslaver,
threatening our peace.
His reign was short, huh?
And thanks to this woman,
a great super.
You love her, you missed her.
Welcome back, Elastigirl!
Come on up here.
Don't be bashful.
Come on, get up here.
I want you to have this.
A memento.
Thanks, Winston, Evelyn,
and everyone at Devtech.
I'm forever in your debt.
And thanks to all of you. Your
pressure changed all the right minds.
We made amazing headway
in a very short time,
which leads me to an
important announcement.
Just now, at a world-wide summit,
leaders from more than a hundred
of the world's top countries
have agreed to make
superheroes legal again!
We'll gather superheroes
and leaders
from all over the planet
on our boat the Everjust,
for a televised signing
ceremony at sea!
Now, if you'll excuse us,
we got a ship to catch!
Hey, hi... me again...
Um, there's ... something
I've always wanted to ask you.
How do you balance the superhero
stuff with the life stuff?
*I'd really like to know.
Uhuh... Oh, would you, please,
excuse me for a moment?
Yeah, OK, see you later. Good talk.
- Hey, Vi.
- Hey.
- Where's Jack-Jack?
- E's taking him for a little bit.
- Edna is babysitting?
- Yeah.
And you're OK with this?
Yeah, I dunno why.
I wanted to say something to you.
Sorry about Tony.
I didn't think about
Dicker erasing his memory,
or about you having to pay
the price for a choice
you never made.
It's not fair, I know.
And then I made it worse at the
restaurant by trying to ...
Anyway, anyway...
I'm sorry.
I'm used to knowing what
the right thing to do is.
But now, I'm not sure, anymore.
I just wanna be...
a good dad.
You're not good,...
you're super.
Are superheroes allowed to
drink on duty?
I am, definitely, not on duty.
Ignore the costume.
I know, I should be up there,
but, I had to step away from
the 'grip and grins', you know?
Gotta get away to keep it pure.
I know I do.
What are you getting away from?
Eh, you know, company stuff.
My brother, mostly.
But you love him.
You two are this company.
Yin and Yang.
Yeah, I invent the stuff,
he's good at people:
pleasing them, engaging them,
figuring out what they want.
I never know what people want.
What do you think they want?
Ease. People will trade quality
for ease, every time.
It may be crap, but,
hey, it's convenient!
Yeah, kinda like this case.
- What the Screenslaver?
- Yeah, something doesn't seem right.
It was too easy.
That was too easy?
- Finally.
- What?
What is that?
It's one of the Screenslaver's
monitors it's tuned into my suit-cam.
- Isn't the suit-cam closed circuit?
- Yes.
Then, how come the Screenslaver has it?
Maybe he hacked it?
So, he's sophisticated enough
to do that,
but he has simple locks
on his doors?
Maybe he wanted you to find him.
He wanted to get caught?
- He wanted you to win.
- That makes no sense.
He's a brilliant guy. If he's smart enough
to conceive of technology like this,
he's smart enough think of
something to do with it.
The guy we put put in jail
delivered pizzas.
So? Einstein was a patent clerk! He...
Look, you won.
- You've got the guy...
- Wait!
All Screenslaver needs to do,
to hypnotize someone,
is get a screen in front of their eyes.
But, what if the screen
doesn't look like a screen?
What if... the pizza guy
is really a pizza guy
but, he was controlled by the
screens built into his glasses...?
You are good.
Look, a robot. It's taking off.
I'm not getting a reading, yet.
- Fire?
- Now.
More power.
I hope it works dad.
I thought it was best
to just let you sleep.
17 hours!
How do you feel?
Super.
-You got it, dad!
- Hurray!
I can't tell you how much I appreciate
you watching Jack-Jack for me, E.
Yes, I'm sure your gratitude
is quite inexpressible.
Don't ask me to do it again, darling,
my rates are far too high.
I am joking, Robert,
I enjoyed the assignment.
He is bright and I am stimuated,
we deserve each other.
You child is a polymorph.
Like all babies, he has
enormous potential.
It's not unknown for supers to have
more than one power, when young,
but, this little one has many.
Yes, you have many powers?
Ba ba ba...
I understand your lack of sleep
and coherency, Robert.
Babies can be anything,
and your child is no exception.
He is pure, unlimited potential, Robert.
That's why I worked in a creative fever.
Auntie Edna stayed up
all night,
making sure you look
fabulous in your *new clothes.
What're...
You're putting him in...
In the chamber, Robert.
He is part of the demonstration
and will be fine.
Your challenge is to manage
a baby who has
multiple powers and no control
over them, yes?
Well, uh...That sums it up.
I often work to music, and I noticed
the baby responds to it as well.
Specifically Mozart.
I blended kevlar with carbide for
durability under duress and comfort.
Interwoven with these fabrics,
are a mesh of tiny sensors
that monitor the baby's
physical properties.
Oh Lord ! What's he... what is he doing?
Well, it's Mozart, Robert!
Can you blame him?
The important thing is
that the suit and tracker
anticipated the change
and alerted you.
Oh no! Cookies, I gotta get cookies!
You do not need cookies, as I learned
quite painfully, last night.
Any solution involving cookies will
inevitably result in the demon phase.
"Combustion imminent"?
What does that mean?
It means fire, Robert.
Though, the suit has ...*
I suggest you extinguish
the baby's flames,
before he tests the
sprinkler system.
The flame retardant
is blackberry-lavender foam.
Effective, edible and delicious.
Oh, what do you know?
That, is useful.
Although I have doubtlessly exceded your
expectations for a SINGLE night's work.
the suit and device contain a few
more features we need to discuss.
Thanks again, E, for everything.
- How much do I owe you?
- Oh, pish-posh, darling.
Your bill will be covered by my fee
for being Mr. Incredible, Elastigirl
and Frozone's
exclusive designer throughout
the known universe
and until the end of time.
But babysitting this one,
I do for free, darling.
I would resist the temptation
to stretch,
the temperature around you
is well below freezing.
Try to stretch and you'll break.
So you're the Screenslaver?
Yes... And no.
Let's say, I created the character
and pre-recorded the messages.
Does Winston know?
That I'm the Screenslaver?
Of course not!
Can you imagine what
'Mr. Free Enterprise'
would do with my
hypnosis technology?
Worse than what you're doing?
Hey, I'm using the technology
to destroy people's trust in it.
Like I'm using superheroes.
- Who did I put in jail?
- Pizza delivery guy.
Seemed the right height, build.
He gave you a pretty good fight.
I should say I gave you
a pretty good fight, through him.
But, it doesn't bother you that
an innocent man is in jail?
Eh, he was surly.
And the pizza was cold.
I counted on you.
That's why you failed.
- What?
- Why would you count on me?
Because I built you a bike?
Because my brother knows the words
to your theme song?
We don't know each other.
But you can count on me, anyway.
I'm supposed to, aren't I?
Because you have some strange
abilities and a shiny costume,
the rest of us are supposed to put
our lives into your gloved hands.
That's what my father believed.
When our home was broken into,
my mother wanted to hide.
Begged my father to use
the safe room.
But, father insisted they call
his superhero friends.
He died. Pointlessly.
Stupidly.
Waiting for heroes to save the day.
- But, why would?... Your brother...
- IS A CHILD!
He remembers the time when we had
parents AND superheroes.
So, like a child,
Winston conflates the two.
Mommy and Daddy went away,
because supers went away.
Our sweet parents were fools to put
their lives in anybody else's hands.
Superheroes keep us weak!
Are you gonna kill me?
Nah.
Using you, is better.
You're gonna help me
make supers illegal,
forever.
- Ready? - Ga.
- Laser eyes.
- Stop!
- Wow!
Yay, Jack-Jack!
That's not all. Watch this.
Jack-Jack, blaster ready?
- No way?!
- Crazy cool!
- I get to fire him now!
- Hey, it's demonstration!
No firing the baby around the house,
you understand?
This is potentially dangerous.
We're trying to teach him
to control his powers, OK?
Stop! See the screen?
He vanished!
That's really cool!
OK, good. Use the thing.
See that's called a readout.
Click it. See the readout? Dimension 4.
See the shape? That's the room.
See where he is in relation?
So, where is he?
There!
OK, come out. Num-num, cookie?
- Yayy! - Jack-Jack!
- Really cool!
- Hello?
- Elastigirl's in trouble.
What? What happened to her?
Sorry, to tell you on the phone.
Meet me on our ship at Devtech.
The ship at Devtech.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
What's with the ship at Devtech?
Lucius? Bob. Helen's in trouble.
I need someone to watch the kids.
- Suit up, it might get weird.
- I'll be there, ASAP, 15 tops.
Where are you going, ASAP?
And wearing that suit?
I gotta go. Be home soon.
Lucius will be here, sooner.
No firing the baby
around the house, OK?
What's at the ship at Devtech?
And why are you in your super suit?
Is that mom's super suit?
She may need it. You never know.
What's going on?
I dunno. But dad called Lucius
AFTER getting a call about mom,
and then LEFT.
I thought you renounced superheroes.
Yeah, well, I renounce my
renunciation!
Put that on.
Hello there, little fella.
Hello.
You kids aren't safe.
- The Deavors sent us to take you...
- Well, isn't that redundant!
The Deavors just sent ME here
to guard the house.
'Cause the kids aren't safe.
I get it, managerial screw-up.
Tell Winston, I have this*.
You understand, Ms? ...
Voyd.
Ms. Voyd!
*I'll see-ya.
But, the thing is,
he wants us to bring you, too.
Hey!
That isn't gonna hold them long.
Dash, grab the baby!
Spread out!
Dash, we gotta get to my car!
What? What's going on?
Little fella?
It worked!
Incredibile, windows down!
Climb in!
Incredibile, transfer driver identification
Loudly, say your names!
- Violet Parr.
- Dashiell Robert Parr.
- Lucius!
- Harrgh!
Incredibile, escape!
- Fill me in.
- Good news and bad news.
We found her, she seems physically
fine but she's had an ecounter
with Screenslaver and she's
acting kinda strange.
In here.
Strange, how?
Helen?
Helen, what are you?...
Helen, it's me.
Incredibile, pull over.
We can't go to E's.
You saw those goggles
they put on Lucius,
they were wearing them, too.
They're all under someone's control.
They've probably done the same
to mom.
OK, bad guys after us,
no mom, no dad, no Lucius.
But, we have our powers, this car
and...
what?
Incredibile, take us to Devtech!
Kids have escaped in a tricked out car,
but we got Frozone.
Bring him to the ship at Devtech,
immediately.
Aww! We missed'em.
Oh, I wish the Incredibile
could follow that boat.
- What did you do?
- I dunno.
- I didn't do anything!
Wow, this car does anything I say!
- We didn't plan this, well.
- What do you mean? We're here, aren't we?
Yes, we're here.
We need to be up there.
Hm...
I think, the Incredibile has
ejector seats.
Wait, what? No.
- Yeah, baby, let's go!
- No, no.
Come on.
Hello, glad you could come.
- Welcome to the conference.
- Good to be here.
Our stars, where are they?
The event's about to start.
They didn't want to upstage
the others.
They'll join for the signing.
Welcme guests, you're in for a treat.
This ship is the largest hydrofoil
on the planet.
So, hold onto something because
we're gonna open her up!
We need to find mom and dad.
Stay here, I'm gonna
search for them.
Wait, who's gonna watch Jack-Jack?
Suck it up, I won't be long.
Wait. What? But, but... Wait!
This is important,
they are in trouble.
It's up to us.
'To us', understand?
Keep him amused, but quiet!
Ohhh...
Jack-Jack?
Jack-Jack? Jack-Jack!
- Jack-Jack.
- *Now, the supers know we're here.
But, I found mom and dad.
- Where is Jack-Jack?
- I dunno.
You lost him?
I gave you one thing to do!
The tracker. Use the tracker.
- He's going up?
- He's in an elevator.
Let's go!
Hey, little baby,
where are your paren...?
And here they are, folks!
The supers who started
this whole thing.
I told you they'd be there in time.
Hey, did you make them new masks?
Yeah, night vision, etcetera...
They look, good, right?
So simple, even he can do it.
And we're back, live, in ...
3, 2, 1.
This is a momentous occasion.
We've all managed to
accomplish something
extraordinarily rare
in today's world:
we agree on something.
We agree to undo a bad decision.
To make sure a few
extraordinarily gifted members
of the world's many countries
are treated fairly.
To invite them once again,
to use their gifts to benefit the world.
I thank all of you
for representing your nation's
commitment to superheroes.
With special thanks to
Ambassador Salomon.
Yup, it's OK, let her hear you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Ambassador,
for your early and very crucial support.
I can't think of anyone
more deserving than you
to be the first signature on the
International Superhero Accord.
There it is.
Holy cow!
- *He's always on fire.
- Just put him out!
They're coming.
Is he okay?
*Yeah, unless you have a beter idea.
No!
Come on, Jack-Jack, we have to go.
Cookie, num-num?
- I see him. He's getting away.
- Stand back!
- Darn it.
- He's heading for mom.
It is done, the world is super again!
Group photo, come on.
Group photo, everyone.
Squeeze in, that's it, historic occasion.
Everyone smile.
Go for Phase 2.
Years of mandated hiding and
silence have made us bitter.
You bring us out into the light,
only to clean up the messes your
lack of discipline creates.
Your bodies and your
character are weak.
Your promises are empty
and you will pay for it.
We no longer serve you.
We serve only us.
May the fittest survive.
Well, we, uh...
Some very alarming moments there...
before the technical difficulties.
Please, bear with us.
- Mayday, mayday, mayday ...
- Hold it. Let him talk.
Superheroes have forcibly
taken the bridge. Repeat:...
Now!
A little further...
Stop!
What the? A baby?!
Mom and dad! Uncle Lucius?
Jack-Jack, no!
A, superbaby? No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, put him down!
- Grab her!
- Mom. - Get Jack-Jack to safety!*
NO!
- Hey, it's me!
- Yeah, that's what I thought, last time.
What?...
You came for us?
- Don't be mad.
- Oh sweetie.
How could I be mad?
I'm proud.
Not to break up a tender moment,
but,
where are we?
Is this Devtech's ship?
Evelyn Deavor, controls
the Screenslaver,
and until a second ago, us.
- Where the crew?
- Collision detected, correct course.
- Did I do that?
- Mom?
Here, try this.
Collision detected, correct course.
Phase 3. Go on phase 3!
Why are the kids here?
You didn't go to the house?
I went to the house!
You didn't escape?
- How did you not escape?
- Hey, we saved you!
Escape? Escape from what?
Those guys!
Jack-Jack, has powers?!
We know. Fight, now, talk later.
Laser eyes.
Oh!
- Come with me, Winston.
- Did I faint?
- You'll be safe here.
- Safe? Safe from what?
- What about those diplomats and the supers?
- Still hypnotized.
What have you done?
Evelyn. She's escaping!
Well, go after her.
Finish your mission.
I can't just go.
What about the kids? Jack-Jack?
- Who's gonna?...
- Mom!
Go! We've got this.
Voyd, come with me.
- I'll go shut down the engine.
- I'll try to to slow the ship from the bow.
Wait, something's missing.
Where the Crusher gone?
Strap in, now!
It's for your own good.
NO!
This is!
- Were too late.
- Get me up to the jet.
Hey, you did this. Can you undo it?
You want me to un-crush?
What, no one's ever asked
for that?
No, to un-crush is silly!
Why un-crush?
To get into the engine room. Aw,
forget, it, we don't have enough time.
What if I said to un-punch someone?
What you do?
Welcome aboard Elastigirl.
Although, we haven't yet
reached our cruising altitude...
feel free to roam about the cabin.
Or, just relax and let things happen.
We're all about you.
- I can't get to the engine room.
- Well, we gotta to do something.
'Cause trying to slow it down
ain't working.
- Hey, what about turning the boat?
- The steering's been destroyed.
- Dash means, from the outside.
- Yeah!
If we break off one of the
foils arnd turn the rudder
we can steer the ship
away from the city.
- That might work.
- I'll turn the front, you turn the rear.
Using the rudder?
That's under water!
How am I supposed to?...
Oh, great.
- Come on, kids.
- Dad!
I know this is going to work,
but, if it doesn't, and we crash,
my shields are probably better
protection than the ship.
I should stay here, with Jack-Jack.
That's my girl.
Remember Bob,
we're both turning right.
You know what's sad?
If it weren't for your core beliefs,
I think we copuld've been
good friends.
I wish I ha...
had core beliefs.
We have breaking news.
While there is still no radio contact,
the ship has changed direction
and is heading towards land
at a high rate of speed.
Dash.
I am going to the rudder.
Once I turn the ship,
you hit the pull up button.
- OK, dad.
- Now, lower me dow ...
The reputations of superheroes
are ruined.
You will never become legal.
Ever!
- Never?
- No.
- Ever?
- No!
Not even a little smidgie-widgie?
Ah, hypoxia!
When you don't have enough oxygen
things seem incredibly silly.
Things get sillier and sillier
and then you die.
- I don't wanna die.
- Ah, nobody does.
Really.
Not such a bad way to go.
Everyone, we need to get
to the back of the ship.
All supers protect
your ambassadors.
Follow!
Dad's been underwater for too long.
Gotta pull him up!
Wait, it's too soon.
- I'm gonna press the button!
- Not yet!
It's turning. It's working!
- Now!
- Dash, now!
Save yourself, make a chute.
Make a chute. Make a chute!
Dash, brace yourself!
*We're out of position!
I missed Jack-Jack's first power?
Actually, you missed the first 17.
Oh!
The fact you saved me
doesn't make you right.
- But, it does make you alive.
- And I'm grateful for that.
I'm sorry, but she'll go to prison.
Well, I'm sorry, she's rich
and will probably get
no more than a slap on the wrist.
First of all, Violet I like you.
And who knows what the
future may bring?
But, I have a good feeling
about all of you.
Good feeling?
Should we be worried?
You guys got the next shift.
Come here.
I saw what you did back there,
that was incredible.
- I mean, no pun intended.
- Sorry I had to punch you.
Ah, finally my sweet ride!
And in recognition of the extraordinary
service they have demonstrated,
the legal status of superheroes
is hereby restored.
- You don't know me, do you?
- No, I don't, wait ...
- Are you the girl with the water...?
- I'm Violet Parr.
I'm Tony.
- Tony, this is my mom.
- Pleased to meet you.
- It's my dad.
- Oh, we've met.♥
- This is embarrassing.
- Charmed, I'm sure.
My little brother Dash.
And baby is Jack-Jack.
I tried to limit it
to ONE parent.
We're all going to a movie, too, Tony.
Don't mind us.
We'll be sitting on the other
side of theater.
- Not watching you.
- Hah!
H-He's kidding, they're only
dropping us off at the theater.
They have OTHER things to do.
- So, you guys are close, I guess.
- Yeah, I guess.
- We can get closer.
- Bob.
Stop! Let us out.
Here: large popcorn, small soda,
save me a seat. *...
I'll be back before the
previews are over.
♪Subtitles by♪  XQ2☻♥
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6n4ja
Help other users to choose the best subtitles